fitlads.net 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Fitlads Help

The following is our Privacy policy. Please note it is liable to change without prior notice.

## Data Protection

We are registered under the Data Protection Act. Our registration number is [Z969311X](http://www.ico.gov.uk/ESDWebPages/search.asp)

Fitlads complies with the eight principles of the Data Protection Act, which ensure that personal information is:

  1. Fairly and lawfully processed
  2. Processed for limited purposes
  3. Adequate, relevant and not excesive
  4. Accurate and up to date
  5. Not kept for longer than is necessary
  6. Processed in line with your rights
  7. Secure
  8. Not transferred to other countries without adequate proection. (In fact we don't transfer it outside the UK at all).

## What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

  * Information about your visits to this website, including your IP address, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views
  * Information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make
  * Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us, such as your email address and mobile number (if you provided it)
  * Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and newsletters

## Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by Fitlads to your web browser and stored by your browser. This information is then sent back to Fitlads each time your request a page on our website. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. Fitlads uses this to maintain your unique user session.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. [Click here for Google's privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

## Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you:

  * To the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  * In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  * In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

__

Still need help? Contact Us Contact Us

Last updated on December 12, 2013
